If you lose to me,
I'll take your left arm.
Well, not to be rude,
but instead of my left arm,
do you think that it'd be okay
if just bet the same thing
Usually?
And what is that?
I bet my life.
Your life, huh?
I'm just beginning to realize
it was I who lacked resolve.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
KNOV X AND X MOREL
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
while Knov uses this opportunity
to infiltrate the palace.
[thunder rumbling]
[Knov panting]
Finally, I made it.
The stairs are still
over a hundred meters away.
Giant fruit on bizarre trees,
About 500 on each one…
And 10 trees totals 5,000.
But after only one day,
Killua's interference
brought the process to a grinding halt,
so it adds up.
These cocoons hold the selected humans.
Neferpitou is probably a Manipulator,
and, if so, almost certainly intends
to manipulate these soldiers
into invading the rest of the world
as per the King's will.
The palace entrance looks dark.
No one's there.
So far, so good.
Middle exit. Set.
Now for the near exit.
I don't see any guards anywhere.
I'd wager that there's only
a select few waiting inside.
KING
We must delay any reinforcements,
even if only for a second.
CENTRAL STAIRCASE
The first floor is too far.
The central stairway, second floor,
that's the best location.
The central staircase
is beyond this courtyard.
Should I make one here, just in case?
No, that would be no different
from the one outside.
I have to at least get close
to the first floor's central staircase,
preferably up the stairs
on the second floor.
Hmm? [gasps]
[Knov] Scream.
[Nen whooshing]
Are there any others around?
If they saw me, it's over.
[panting]
I'll have to retreat.
[sighs]
So it was alone.
[gasps]
It's like it's full of
everything sinister in the world.
It's not that I fear death, not anymore.
What I fear most
is that the ones lurking up there
would go to great lengths
to wring out any info I have on the King
before killing me,
which they would do
in the cruelest way they could think of.
If I'm caught, I won't be able to resist.
[exhales]
[rain pattering]
Huh?
You look familiar.
Aren't you that lion guy I saw on TV?
My name is Leol, and don't you forget it.
I was told that I should expect
to meet up with a wolf and a lobster.
I'm afraid that those two are busy
dealing with the grunts you created,
which means I can fight you one-on-one.
I do appreciate the personal attention.
This guy's just as strong as Cheetu.
No, he's a little stronger.
Now, let's get started.
[Morel] Allowing Knov
to get into the palace is my top priority.
I need to focus on
keeping the enemy's attention.
[growls] That's not gonna help.
there are also women inside.
Not for the King
but for the lecherous
Director Bizeff himself.
If our strategy worked,
Palm is among them.
You can leave the fourth truck
right there.
[Marcos] Yes, sir.
And, now, if you would please excuse us.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[whistling a tune]
[whistling continues]
[slurps]
[engine turns off]
[chuckles]
You have but one job while you're here,
and that is to carry out all of my orders.
When you are summoned,
you must drop everything
and come to see me at once.
[women] Yes, Director, sir.
[Bizeff] Excellent.
-You there.
-[gasps]
And, as for the rest of you ladies,
you can go wait in your rooms.
[women] Right.
We made the cut. We made it.
Oh, we must have caught his fancy.
[both laughing]
[Palm] I have to find a way out of here.
I must see the King
and his Royal Guards myself.
[narrator] Once Palm has seen a person
up close and with her own eyes,
[panting]
[shivering]
that… that vicious Aura…
[crying] One glance
You may have even touched it.
[sobbing]
How could you still face them?
How?
Palm! [sobbing]
Please, don't push your luck.
Please, I'm begging you.
Hmm?
It's almost too perfect
that, after all that running,
the perfect location
for your painfully violent death.
Sorry, but you'll have to say
your own prayers.
You see, I'm an atheist.
[chuckles]
That's pretty optimistic of you.
Now, let's see which of us
is really cornered.
[exhales]
Hmm?
[grunts]
[Morel] So he led me here
knowing full well?
[chuckles] Works for me.
If he believes
that everything is going his way,
he won't hesitate
to put his own abilities on display.
But I've seen some flexible abilities
in my time,
and not a single one of them
could hold a candle to my Deep Purple.
I feel tingly.
I love it, the moment
an opponent showcases their abilities.
It's addictive.
Still, it might make more sense to attack
before he reveals what he can do.
But no, that's not how a man fights.
Check out their second album.
That one is the coolest.
The 12 songs on it form a story,
is that the album's
exactly 60 minutes long.
It's a classic.
Yeah. I hate to say it, but you're right.
[Morel] This is bad.
[closing theme song playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, Return and Retire.
Killua! Killua!
[Killua] Return on! To the preview!
[Gon crying] It has to be you, Killua!
[Killua] Hey, stop crying.
[singer singing in Japanese]